fiction 
4

Get Outlook for Android <https://aka.ms/ghei36> 



Be green - keep it on the screen.
This email and any files transmitted with it are confidential and intended solely for the use of the individual to whom they are addressed. If you are not the named addressee please notify the sender immediately and delete it from your system. Any person forwarding a message accepts responsibility for its content. Any views or opinions presented are solely those of the author.

________________________________

The John of Gaunt School is a company limited by guarantee. Registered office: Wingfield Road, Trowbridge, Wiltshire, BA14 9EH. Company number: 7990655. 